{
  "response.id": 1,
  "questionnaire.id": 1001,
  "questionnaire.name": "My Sample Question",
  "questiongroups": [
    {
      "questiongroup.id": 1001,
      "questiongroup.name": "questiongroup name one",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question.id": 1001,
          "question.manadatory": "TRUE",
          "question.code": "Q1",
          "question.position": 1,
          "question.help": "Please used the following  scoring system  Score of 1 -  Dont Like Score of 3  - See Some Value Score of 5  -  Great Tool",
          "question": "What is our evaluation of the Jhipster 3.x Application.",
          "question.type": "5 Point Choice",
          "response": "3"
        },
        {
          "question.id": 1002,
          "question.manadatory": "TRUE",
          "question.code": "Q2",
          "question.position": 2,
          "question.help": "For each Subquestion (Row) select the best Aswer (Column)",
          "question": "A Array Question Type uses Subquestions (Rows) and Answer Options (Columns)",
          "question.type": "array",
          "subquestion": [
            {
              "subquestion.id": 1001,
              "subquestion.code": "Sub1",
              "subquestion.position": 1,
              "subquestion": "Subquestion One.",
              "response": "Answer One"
            },
            {
              "question.id": 1002,
              "question.code": "Sub2",
              "question.position": 2,
              "subquestion": "Subquestion two.",
              "response": "Answer Two"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questiongroup.id": 1002,
          "questiongroup.name": "questiongroup name one",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question.id": 1003,
              "question.manadatory": "TRUE",
              "question.code": "Q2",
              "question.position": 1,
              "question.help": "This is a mulitple Options Question with comments.",
              "question": "Check that all that apply (Columns)",
              "question.type": "Multiple choice with Comments",
              "subquestion": [
                {
                  "subquestion.id": 1003,
                  "subquestion.code": "Sub1",
                  "subquestion.position": 1,
                  "subquestion": "I am Glad.",
                  "response": "TRUE",
                  "comment": " "
                },
                {
                  "subquestion.id": 1004,
                  "subquestion.code": "Sub2",
                  "subquestion.position": 2,
                  "subquestion": "I dont care.",
                  "response": "FALSE",
                  "comment": "comment here"
                },
                {
                  "subquestion.id": 1005,
                  "subquestion.code": "Sub3",
                  "subquestion.position": 3,
                  "subquestion": "I am happy",
                  "response": "TRUE",
                  "comment": " "
                },
                {
                  "subquestion.id": 1006,
                  "subquestion.code": "Sub4",
                  "subquestion.position": 4,
                  "subquestion": "Other",
                  "response": "Other Text",
                  "comment": " "
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "question.id": 1004,
              "question.manadatory": "FASLE",
              "question.code": "Q2",
              "question.position": 2,
              "question.help": "Please allow user to save with as formatted text.",
              "question": "Describe something with formated Text",
              "question.type": "Multiple choice with Comments",
              "response": "HTML Formatted TEXT Goes Here"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}